艾瑪去哪了 艾瑪
-Where's Emma? Emma?!
艾瑪 艾瑪
Emma! Emma!
艾瑪 你在哪里 親愛的 艾瑪
Emma, where are you, honey?  Emma?
艾瑪
Emma?
上帝  我天
Oh God. Oh my God.
你還好嗎 哦 上帝
Are you okay?  Oh God.
好了 沒事了
Okay. Okay.
哦  謝天謝地
Oh, thank God.
我看到了一個可怕的男人
I saw a scary man.
既不是命運也不是現實
Neither fate nor society
允許弗朗西斯•穆里根
put Francis Mulligan  in the house
就在15日晚上 闖入凱萊•米切爾的家
of Gloria Mitchell  on the night of the 15th.
既不是命運也不是現實
Neither fate nor society
叫他把她綁起來  用槍指著她
told him to tie her up,  shove a gun in her face
竊取她的財物
and steal her belongings.
那是他自己的選擇
That was his choice.
辯方還會站在被告一方么
The defense would have you  walk in his client's shoes.
嗯  我會
Well, I have.
我來自里佛岱爾
I'm from Riverdale.
這是一個craphole
It's a craphole.
沒人說它不是  可...
Nobody's saying  it's not, but...
我就是來自那里 不是我是誰
that's where I'm from.  It's not who I am.
他不是受害者
He is not the victim here.
所以 如果你們要站在任何一方...
So if you are gonna put yourself in anyone's shoes...
請...
put yourself...
站在凱萊•米切爾一方
in Gloria Mitchell's.
謝謝
Thank you.
陪審團現在休會 稍后宣判
The jury will now adjourn  to deliberate a verdict.
尼斯來了 看著你呢 前五排
Nice close.  Straight to your top five.
-你喜歡這樣 -是的 我做到了
-You like that? -Yeah, I did.
"不是我是誰 " 這句非常經典
"Not who I am."  That was very cute.
-我得走了  -米奇 陪審團剛剛離開
-I gotta go.  -Mitch, the jury only just left.
有罪 五年 兩年后假釋
Guilty, five years, parole after two.
-你怎么知道的  -第一 法官被我的
-How do you know that?  -One, the judge is soft
有教養的論述所感化 而且沒人中槍
on the educationally-challenged and nobody got shot.
第二呢
And two?
我不會輸的
I don't lose.
嗯 就算那么回事吧
Well, that part's true.
-這就是我恨你的原因  -晚上見
-That's why I hate you.  -See you tonight.
-往上看 看著我
-Look up. Look up.
-茄子
-Please.
-再來一張  -不要  別拍了
-One more.  -No. Absolutely not.
-手那么小小的  -我知道
-Look at those tiny little hands.  -I know.
我不能相信她看起來如此完美
I can't believe her. Looks so perfect.
她是那么安靜
She's so peaceful.
謝謝
Thank you.
我們是幸福的
We're lucky.
對不起 我得走了 今晚得加班
I'm sorry I have to go  to this work thing tonight.
我也希望能在這里陪你
I wish I could  stay here with you.
-扶我下  -小心 這很滑
-Help me.  -Careful, it's slippery.
伙計們 明天見 謝謝你們的酒
Guys.  Tomorrow, thank you.
晚安  伙計們
-Good night, boys.
我他媽的討厭龍舌蘭酒
I fucking hate Tequila!
每個人都討厭龍舌蘭酒  都這么想的
Everybody hates Tequila.  That's the idea.
嗯  我 -我不知道怎么就
Well, I-I didn't know what to get
成為擁有這一切的人  所以
-the man who has everything, so-
這家伙有個好工作  漂亮的小寶寶...
He's got a career, a beautiful little baby...
-哦 我的小親親  -...性感的妻子
-Oh, my little baby.  -...a sexy wife.
-當心  -又打擊我 -
-Careful.-And then it hits me-
我只能借酒消愁
I'm gonna get the man a Tequila hangover.
米奇 明早見
So, Mitch, tomorrow morning,
你會醒來的 我的朋友
you are gonna wake up  complete, my friend.
是的
That's right.
-謝謝你 謝謝  -我幫過
-Thank you. Thank you.  -I helped.
沒問題
Complete.
你一個人回家 沒事吧
You okay getting home?
是啊 我打輛車
Yeah. Gonna get a-
-出租車  -好吧
-gonna get a cab.  -All right.
-哦
-Oh.
-喂  -這里是對方付費電話
-Hello?  -This is a collect call
來自協和監獄的一個犯人
from an inmate at Concord penitentiary.
-要接受此呼叫  請按1  -
-To accept this call, press 1.
-沒事吧  -沒事
-Everything okay?  -Yeah.
是啊  唉  明天見
Yeah.Ugh.See you tomorrow.
聽著 半夜你要是酒勁上來
Listen, when you throw up in the middle of the night,
-嘔吐時遠離寶寶  -知道  我會的
-aim away from your baby.  -Yeah, I will.
-要吐時遠離寶寶  -遠離寶寶
-Aim away from the baby.  -Away from the baby.
我答應
I promise.
不要在吐在孩子身上 米奇
Don't puke on  your child, Mitch.
-我不會的  -明天見
-I won't puke on my child. -Until tomorrow.
明天見
Tomorrow.
別遲到
Don't be late!
城內的出租車
Inner-City taxi.
-嘿
-Hey!
-城內的出租車 喂
-Inner-City taxi. Hello?
要我幫你們么
Can I help you guys?
他媽的想干什么
What the fuck?
哦  他媽的
Oh, fuck it.
混蛋
Fuck.
什么情況
What the fuck?
哦  天
Oh no.
哦  他媽的 哦
Oh fuck. Oh fuck.
哦  對不起  我不是故意的
Oh, I'm so sorry.  I'm so sorry.
哦  媽的  我很抱歉
Oh fuck.  I'm so sorry.
-哦  媽的
-Oh shit.
嘿  我會叫救護車的
Hey, I'll get an ambulance.
哦  他媽的  哦  混蛋
Oh fuck.  Oh fuck.
先蓋上
Take this.
沒關系 我會求救的
It's okay. I'm gonna get help.
我這就去叫輛救護車 沒事吧 堅持住
I'm gonna get an ambulance, all right? Hold in there.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
嘿 就兩分鐘  我保證
Hey. Two minutes.  I promise.
-不要丟下我  -我只是去叫救護車
-Don't leave me.  -Just gonna call an ambulance.
兩分鐘內我會回來的
I'll be back in two minutes.
這是911 你有什么緊急情況
911, what's your emergency?
我需要一輛救護車  一位男士被車撞了
I need an ambulance.  A guy's been hit by a car.
-現在什么位置 先生  -呃  基勒
-What's the location, sir?  -Uh, Keeler.
-基勒和第26街之間  -你叫什么名字  先生
-Keeler and 26th.  -What's your name, sir?
請抓緊時間 快點 他受了重傷
Please just hurry. Hurry, he's hurt real bad.
先生
Sir.
救護車已經在路上了
The ambulance is coming.
-不要離開我  -我得走了 我不能留在這
-Don't leave me.  -I have to go. I can't stay.
我不能留下來 你會沒事的
I can't stay.  You'll be fine.
我保證 我保證 對不起
I promise. I promise.  I'm sorry.
-不要丟下我  -我得走了
-Please. No.  -I have to go.
-救救我  -不要 救救我
-Please.  -Please. Please.
他媽的 他媽的
Fuck. Fuck.
救護車就要來了 明白嗎
An ambulance is coming, okay?
好吧
Okay?
不要離開我 不要
Don't leave me, please.
-爸爸在這 嘿  親  -嘿
-There's daddy. Hey, lover.  -Hey.
你在干什么
What on earth are you doing up?
-沒有睡好  -宿醉
-I didn't sleep great.  -Hangover?
是啊
Yeah.
你怎么樣
How are you?
還好吧  小家伙每一  二個小時就要吃
Well, apparently they wake up every  two hours and they demand food.
-誰知道 -我能做什么
-Who knew?  -Can I help?
是的 你可以修修車庫門 快把我逼瘋了
Yes,you could fix the garage doors.They're driving me crazy.
搶購一些尿布
Just gonna grab some diapers.
-米奇  -嗯
-Mitch. -Uh-huh.
有什么想告訴我
Something you wanna tell me?
什么
What?
昨晚
About last night?
-什么 -車子么
-What?  -And the car?
瑞...
Rach...
呃...
uh...
車子怎么停在車庫里
And why it's parked  in the garage?
你開車回家嗎
Did you drive home?
是啊
Yeah.
-你答應坐出租車  -我知道了
-You promised to take a cab. -I know.
不 我的意思是 你瘋了嗎
No, I mean-What, are you crazy?
因為如果你得到一個D.U.I.(類似酒駕)
'Cause if you get a D.U.I.,
那么你要和D.A.辦公室說再見
then you can kiss  the D.A.'s office goodbye.
我知道了 我知道 我很抱歉
I know. I know, I'm sorry.
我不應該  不會再這樣了
I shouldn't have. I won't do it again.
米奇 我是認真的 你是個父親了 好嗎
Mitch, I am serious.  You're a father now, okay?
你要抓住機會
You can't afford  to take chances.
我知道了 對不起
I know. I'm sorry.
對不起
I'm sorry.
看到了嗎 你看 即使艾拉同意
See?  Look, even Ella agrees.
艾拉
Ella?
你確定嗎
Are you sure?
嗯  嗯  不要改變話題
Mm-hmm.  Don't change the topic.
我不知道怎么辦  如果我失去了你們
I don't know what I'd do  if I lost you guys.
嗯 來爸爸這 我來帶她 你去睡覺
Mmm. Here, let me take her.You go to bed.
去休息會吧
Go get some rest.
去爸爸那里了
There you go. Thanks.
就一個小時
Just an hour.
-嘿  -你還好嗎
-Hey. -You okay?
是啊  你可以打電話給
Yeah.  Could you call around
周邊的醫院和診所么
the local hospitals  and clinics?
我試圖追查一個年輕人
I'm trying to track down  a young man who was involved
昨晚午夜前后交通事故
in a hit-and-run accident  last night around midnight.
-與什么案子有關  -只要告訴我你發現了什么就行
-What case is it connected to?  -Just let me know what you find.
拜托
Thanks.
-早上好  警官  -早上好
-Morning, officers.  -Good morning.
-好 這邊請  -謝謝
-Good. This way.  -Thanks.
本臺記者在警局前發回有關
I'm down here in  front of the police department
一名當地年輕人慘死于一場交通意外的報道
with the story of the tragic  death of this local young man.
昨晚一場似乎普通的交通意外
What started out as a routine  traffic stop last night
演變成可怕的謀殺案的調查
has turned into a gruesome  murder investigation
當警員截停了這輛面包車時
when police officers  stopped this van
就是我身后被警方扣押的車輛
parked behind me  in the police impound
尾燈已經破碎
for nothing more than  a burnt-out taillight.
警員發現車后門附近鮮血淋漓
When they saw blood dripping  from the rear door,
要求司機打開面包車
they demanded  the driver open the van
于是發現了阿克曼的尸體
and it was then they discovered  the body of Cecil Ackerman,
這是一名來自內珀維爾的24歲假釋犯
a 24-year-old parolee  from Naperville.
請不要
Please don't.
司機聲稱他發現了阿克曼
The driver claims  he found Ackerman
躺在路上 表面上看是肇事逃逸
dying in the road  from an apparent hit-and-run
隨后設法送他去醫院
and was merely trying  to get him to the hospital.
這是杰夫•富蘭克林從現場發來的報道
This is Jeff Franklin,  reporting live from the scene.
嘿 律師先生
Hey, counselor.
謝謝
Thanks.
在嗎
Yeah?
-加隆偵探  -是
-Detective Kanon?  -Yeah.
"committed"里有幾個"T "
How many "T"s in "committed"?
-兩個  -該死的文書工作
-Two. -Fucking paperwork.
你來得真是快
You got here fast.
是啊
Yeah.
你說你對阿克曼謀殺有興趣
You said you were interested  in the Ackerman murder?
是的
Yes, I am.
D.A.安排你來處理嗎
D.A. assigned just you?
算是吧  只是預審
Well, it's just  a provisional inquiry.
跟我來
Walk with me.
犯罪嫌疑人名叫  克林頓•戴維斯
Suspect's name is  Clinton Davis.
55歲  汽車修理工
55; Car mechanic;
襲擊罪前科 沒有做案時間
couple of assault charges, nothing he did time for;
沒有親人 妻女被謀殺
no relatives; Wife and daughter were murdered
死于幾年前一個家庭的入侵案件
in a home invasion a few years back.
律師已經來了
Priest was in here already,
說什么他是一個好人  從來沒有傷害過一只蒼蠅
saying what a good guy he is,  how he'd never hurt a fly,
-等等  -他們說的新聞
-et cetera.  -They said on the news
他在路上發現了塞西爾•阿克曼
that he found Cecil  Ackerman in the road.
是的  我們就在那里
Yeah, we've been there.
現場沒有汽車破碎零件  沒血跡
No broken car parts,  no blood that we could see.
是的 雪整夜在下 所以...
Yeah, but the snow thawed overnight, so...
我們已經在戴維斯的衣服找到了阿克曼的血液和頭發
we've got Ackerman's blood and  hair all over Davis's clothes.
在他的面包車的后面 我們找到了沾血的工具和塑料片
We've got the bloody tools and the  plastic sheets in the back of his van.
我們有足夠的證據起訴他
We've got enough to charge him.
你們需要決定  是否足以定罪
You guys need to decide  if it's enough to convict.
-他看起來嚇壞了  -應該是
-He looks terrified. -He should be.
20歲生命在他眼前就此消失
He's staring down 20 to life  for this one alone.
他一個人么
This one
我通過數據庫查了一些關鍵字
I ran some keywords through the database.
標記了一系列謀殺
It flagged a string of unsolved homicides.
你覺得這家伙的是個連環殺手
You think this guy's  a serial killer?
你甚至不知道 他殺死了這個家伙
You don't even know that he killed this guy.
告訴你老板  我們會盡一切力量送他上法庭
Tell your boss we'll send him  everything we got.
-米奇  -我有一個請求  先生
-Mitch.  -I have a request, sir.
謝謝 嘿
Thanks. Hey.
米奇Brockden  D.A.的辦公室
Mitch Brockden,  D.A.'s office.
我的搭檔斯圖爾特•威爾遜
My associate Stuart Wilson.
特里•羅伯茨  公共辯護人辦公室
Terry Roberts, public  defender's office.
我的名片
There you go.
戴維斯先生 我們要問你幾個問題
Mr. Davis, we're going  to ask you a few questions
關于4日晚
about the night of the 4th.
如果你能回答  盡可能準確回答
If you can answer as accurately as possible-
你會是我的檢控官
You're gonna be my prosecutor?
呃  如果按正常程序
Uh, if this goes to trial,
那么 是的  我就是
then yes, I am.
我什么都沒有做  我是無辜的
I didn't do anything.I'm innocent.
你沒有什么就不用擔心
Then you've got nothing to worry about.
好吧  戴維斯先生
Okay, Mr. Davis,
我們開始  告訴我們當晚早些時候
let's start with you telling us where you were
你在哪里
earlier that evening.
下班以后  我去了某個團體
Left work, went to group,
然后開車去兜風
went for a drive.
什么團體
Group?
是啊  我在一些互助團體幫忙
Yeah, I help out at some support groups.
-開車去了哪  -只是去我想去的地方
-And the drive?  -Just something I do.
這不違法吧 對不對
It's not against  the law, right?
我的意思是 難道你們晚上不出去或者開車周邊轉轉
I mean, don't you ever go out and drive around at night?
恕我直言 這是題外話
Due respect, I think that's beside the point.
我不喜歡總呆在家里
I don't like to spend too much time at home.
這會喚起我許多回憶
It brings back memories-
我的妻子和孩子
My wife and child.
嗯  我懂
Uh, yes.
我聽說過關于你家人的事
I heard what happened  to your family.
我 我很抱歉
I'm-I'm sorry.
伊曼紐爾•費萊 槍殺的第二天晚上
Emanuel fryer. Gunned down the next night
襲擊了另外的家庭
attacking someone else's family.
關于受害者我們還知道些什么
What do we know  about the victim?
塞西爾•阿克曼  登記在案的性犯罪者和
Cecil Ackerman-registered sex offender;
兒童性侵 兩項罪名 入獄二年
two counts of child sex abuse; Did two years inside;
三個月前假釋
was only out on parole three months.
所以是一個真正混混
So a real loss to society.
到目前為止 他和戴維斯之間沒找到聯系
So far there's no connection between him and Davis.
-兇手用的什么兇器  -武器
-What about the murder weapon?  -Weapons.
死因法醫也不能確定
The coroner couldn't be exact,
但他認為這些傷口可能是同一作案工具造成
but he suggested these  wounds could be consistent
用的某一種工具或者機器零件
with the type of tools and machine parts
在戴維斯的面包車后備箱里找到
found in the back of Davis's van.
-確定  -是的 他們還發現
-Could be?  -Well, they also found
可見的油污和傷口里的沙子
significant amounts of oil and grit in the wounds,
這證實了戴維斯的肇事逃逸事實
which corroborates Davis's hit-and-run story.
事實上  維克的D.N.A.和血液
True, but the Vic's  D.N.A. And blood were
遍布戴維斯的衣服 他的面包車里也有
all over Davis's clothes, inside his van.
就是那輛 他把阿克曼抬入的面包車
Which could've got there when he lifted Ackerman into his van.
是啊  或許他殺害了他  戴維斯就有兩項罪名
Yeah, or when he murdered him. Davis has two counts
暴力攻擊 而他的家人
-of aggravated assault.  -At a time when his family
在反抗入侵的時候 恰好被謀殺
had just been murdered in a home invasion.
他還沒有過這么多停車票
He hasn't had so much as a parking ticket since.
什么困擾著你 米奇
What's bothering you, Mitch?
我看不出動機
I don't see motive.
剛拿到的音頻文件
Just got this audio file.
這是復制本
Here's the transcript.
這是個911報警電話  有人報告了事故
It was a 911 call. Somebody called in an accident
20分鐘后 也就是戴維斯被捕前
20 minutes before Davis was picked up.
救護車到達事發地點
By the time the ambulance arrived at the location,
現場一個人也沒有
there was no one there.
好的  謝謝
Okay, thank you.
我們有什么辦法找到報案者
Is there any way we can find the caller?
-沒有 他用的是公用電話  -你怎么知道的
-No, he used a payphone.  -How do you know that?
動動腦子 他會在錄音電話中留下姓名么
If he used his cell, it would have his name, phone records.
很好  這是911電話的潛在漏洞
Okay, 911 call's  potentially damaging,
但它不是決定性的
but it's not conclusive.
如果我們不能找到來電者
And if we can't find  the caller,
辨方也找不到
defense probably can't either.
這可能是在芝加哥任何一人
Could be anyone in Chicago.
米奇  那天晚上你在哪里
Mitch, where were you that evening?
-不  米奇醉得話都說不清了
-No, Mitch couldn't string a sentence together
-那晚怎么了 米奇
-that night, right, Mitch?
-是的 謝謝 斯圖  -如果這是肇事逃逸
-Yeah, thanks, Stu.  -If it was a hit-and-run,
那就需要那個肇事者
all it takes is for the guy who hit him
主動承認 否則我們還會陷入僵局
to come forward and confess, and we're dead in the water.
某個人可能這樣做 是吧
What's the likelihood of anybody doing that, huh?
我們能找到足夠證據來定罪
Do we have enough for a conviction?
戴維斯被發現時 死者就在他的面包車里
Davis was found with a dead man in his van.
我們有大量物證
We have a ton of physical evidence.
沒有不在場證明 有暴力犯罪史
No alibi, a documented history of violence
他的公設辯護人太嫩了
and his public defender's still in diapers.
米奇能輕松搞定
Mitch will eat him for breakfast.
先以謀殺罪一項控告他
Charge him, murder one.
是您做的尸檢吧  醫生
You examined  the body, doctor.
以您的的專業判斷
In your professional...  opinion,
死因是什么
what was the cause of death?
顱骨鈍力外傷
Blunt force trauma  to the skull.
那又是什么原因造成的創傷
And what caused that trauma?
死者的頭骨的后面完全粉碎
The back of the skull was badly crushed,
所以很難縮小作案工具的種類
so it's hard to narrow it down to any one item,
但有些痕跡
but some of the marks seemed consistent
與在嫌疑人的面包車發現的錘子
with a hammer found in the suspect's van.
及覆蓋在內飾上油脂和機油似乎是一致的
And the interior was covered  in grease and motor oil,
所以某種在這種環境中暴力的掙扎
so any type of violent  struggle in that environment
可能也引發那些傷口并留下明顯痕跡
could've also caused those wounds and left that trace evidence.
你說 "似乎是一致的 "
You said, "seemed consistent."
是的
That's correct.
您報告中提到的創傷
Your report talks of abrasions
潤滑脂和機油已浸入傷口
and impact wounds with grease  and motor oil in them.
現在 我敢肯定的說
Now the defense I'm sure is gonna argue that-
那些傷口明顯是
those wounds indicate
一輛汽車輾過塞西爾•阿克曼造成
that a car ran over Cecil Ackerman
正如被告的證詞所說
as per the defendant's testimony
剩下的只是...
and that the rest is just...
并不支持的證據
a misinterpretation of the evidence.
我問完了 法官大人
No more questions, your honor.
這里是911 您發生了什么緊急情況
911, what's your emergency?
我需要一輛救護車
I need an ambulance.
-一位男士被車撞了  -事發地點在哪  先生
-A guy's been hit by a car.  -What's the location, sir?
呃  基勒  基勒和第26大街拐角
Uh, Keeler. Keeler and 26th.
你叫什么名字  先生
What's your name, sir?
請快點
Please just hurry.
-快點  他受了重傷  -先生
-Hurry, he's hurt real bad.  -Sir.
這是你的證人 布諾克頓先生
It's your witness, Mr. Brockden.
醫生  陪審團對你的專業上的問題感到陌生
Doctor, the jury will be unfamiliar  with your field of expertise,
所以我會問一個相當簡單的問題
so I'll ask  quite a simple question.
就是法醫語言學究竟有多準確
Just how accurate is forensic linguistics?
-非常準確  -但它不是絕對的
-Extremely.  -But it's not perfect?
對科學來說不存在絕對
Perfection doesn't happen in science.
好吧 就算十分之一吧  那么
Okay. On a sliding scale of one to 10 then-
您可以反對  律師先生
you may want to object, counselor.
我反對 證人不在現場
The witness's field  is not on trial here.
這個問題我問完了 法官大人
I'll withdraw the question, your honor.
您剛才說 您認為
You stated earlier that you believe
來電者是真實的
the caller to be genuine?
因此 我假設您的意思
By this I assume you mean
他報告的是一個真實存在的
he was reporting  a real accident.
正確
Correct.
你能這么說  只是...
And you can tell this just by...
憑他的聲音就可以斷定
hearing his voice?
它其實很復雜  但這是肯定的
It's more complicated than that, but yes.
您可以為我們描述下來電者么
What else can you tell us about the caller?
很難肯定
Hard to be certain
從磁帶上的聲音判斷
from the quality of the tape.
聽起來是一個白人男性 可能在30多歲
Sounded like a white male-possibly in his 30s-
來自芝加哥南部
from the South of Chicago,
但他盡力掩飾口音
but he's tried hard to soften the accent,
不象您 律師先生
not unlike yourself,counselor.
您來自哪里 里弗代爾
Now you're from where, Riverdale?
你說 你很難 告訴某些...
When you say it's hard  to tell for certain...
這磁帶是不清楚的
that the tape is unclear,
它聽起來 是一個白人男性
that it seems to be a white male-
來自底層的種族
The underlying ethnicity
這個很難完全瞞過受過專業訓練的耳朵
is hard to fully hide  from trained ears.
-是的 又一個好記錄  -嗯
-Yes, it's a good recording.  -Uh-huh.
-好的  謝謝  -謝謝你了
-Okay, thank you.  -Thank you too.
-嘿  -員工會議五點開始
-Hey.  -Staff meeting starts in five.
一個不愿留下姓氏叫吉米的 給您來過電話
Someone named Jimmy called,  wouldn't leave a last name.
說是 他出來了 想要見你
Said to tell you he's out and wants to see you.
留下了聯系電話 要發您的手機上
Left a contact number. Do you want  me to get him on the phone for you?
不 不用 謝謝你
No no no, thank you.
聞到了嗎
Smell that?
這就是自由的味道
That's the smell of freedom.
嘿  那天我給你家去過電話
Hey, so I called your house the other day,
你知道  找過你的
you know, looking for ya.
你的妻子...
Your wife...
她不知道我是誰  是嗎
she doesn't know who I am, does she?
你已經走了很長時間了  吉米
You've been gone a long time, Jimmy.
怎么不告訴她  你有他媽的兄弟
How do you not tell her about your own fucking brother?
同母異父的
Step-brother.
面對現實吧  法律上不承認
And let's face it, legally not even that.
-你想玩什么  -不要他媽的裝可愛  吉米
-You wanna play like that.  -Don't be fucking cute with me, Jimmy.
我在倉庫工作
I was working at that warehouse
掙錢上法律學校的時候 你他媽在哪
to pay my way through law school when you fucking hit it!
我不是一直在做他媽的配件 不是么
I could've been done as a fucking accessory. Huh?
-讓你的工作見鬼去  -是啊 我知道 我他媽真傻
-Bye-bye, career.  -Yeah, I know. I was fucking stupid.
媽的  米奇
Fuck, Mitch.
我的意思是 那個時候是帶過很多藥回來
I mean, Jesus, I was doing a lot of drugs back then.
我是自私
I was selfish.
我有很多他媽的時間
I've had a lot of fucking time
想想我的生活  想想我是誰
to think about my life, think about who I was.
好嗎
Okay?
現在  我讓你失望
Now I let you down.
但我不會再讓你們失望了
But I will not let you down again.
知道么...
Look...
我畢業時遇到了雷切爾
I met Rachel when I was graduating.
她接受了我的申請  到了D.A.辦公室
She processed my application to the D.A.'s office.
自從我的媽媽嫁給你爸
Seeing as my ma never officially married your dad-
是啊 你想通 為什么提我們
yeah, you figured  why mention us, right?
吉米  最好我們不要再有聯系
Jimmy, it was best for me not to have ties
案子已經結了 知道嗎
to a criminal past, you know?
我曾經撒過謊
Once I'd lied on the forms,
-我不知道  -是啊  我明白了
-I couldn't tell  -yeah, I get it.
我明白了
I understand.
-上帝  -我不再是那個家伙了
-God.  -I'm not that kid anymore.
這是... 河谷
Riverdale, it's...
這是另一種生活
It was another life.
好吧  你真幸運
Well, lucky you.
我只得到一個
I only got the one.
別走
Hey.
喂
Hello?
嘿  布諾克頓先生  我是加隆
Hey, Mr. Brockden. It's Kanon.
加隆警官你好
Detective Kanon.
要我做什么
What can I do for you?
在查點東西
Just checking in.
我們失去了一個或兩個支持者
We lost a point or two
因為那個法醫語言學家
on that forensic linguist.
是啊
Yeah.
是啊  我知道了 這是  嗯 -
Yeah, I know. It's, umm-
戴維斯不可能是那個打電話的  所以...
it's almost impossible to make  Davis the caller, so...
是么
Right.
這么晚了  偵探
It's kinda late, detective.
是否有您所需要的
Is there something you need?
沒有  只是想知道
No, just wanted to know
你在為明天上庭做準備
that you're ready for tomorrow.
-什么意思 -什么什么
-What was that?  -What?
你正在錄音
You're recording this?
我為什么要錄音
Why would I be recording this?
他們說警察很執著
They say that cops are paranoid.
法庭上見
See you in court.
嘿 她是睡著了
She's asleep. Hey.
嘿
Hey.
你身上有股奶味
You smell like milk.
艾拉又吐奶了
Ella was sick on me, again.
尼斯
Nice.
米奇
Mitch. Hey.
看我
Look at me.
米奇
Mitch.
怎么了
What is it?
有什么事瞞著我
Is there something you're not telling me?
是
Yes.
什么 你就不能...
What?  Can't you just...
告訴我嗎
Tell me?
我愛你
I love you.
我也愛你
I love you too.
全體起立
All rise.
請座
Be seated.
會議開始前 法官大人
Before session begins, your honor,
我寧愿去替補席
I would like to approach the bench.
我也不能容忍羅伯茨先生遲到
I will not tolerate tardiness, Mr. Roberts.
對不起  法官大人 我早就來了
I'm sorry, your honor, but there has been
案情有重要的進展
an important development.
我們希望 調用一個新的證據
Defense would like to call a new witness.
我反對 法官大人 控方沒有事先告知
Objection, your honor.The prosecution wasn't informed of this.
控方也是昨天深夜才找到的
Defense was unaware of their identity until late last night.
是什么重要證人 羅伯茨先生
What is the relevance of this witness, Mr. Roberts?
他就是給911打電話的人
He's the man who made the 911 call.
-什么 什么情況 -肅靜
-What? What?  -Order!
肅靜
Order.
-法官大人 -我贊同并允許  布諾克頓
-Your honor--I'm inclined to allow it, Mr. Brockden.
是的  我理解  但如果你能 -
Yes, I understand that,but if you could just-
-布諾克頓先生  -布朗博士的實驗室
-Mr. Brockden!  -Dr. Brown's lab
進行了一整夜語音分析  我們找到了一個匹配的
ran a voice analysis overnight and we got a viable match.
這名證人何時能到庭
How soon can defense present this witness?
馬上  法官大人 他整個審判
Right away, your honor.  He's been in the courtroom
一直在法庭上
this entire trial.
我只是要說
Can I just please say some-
夠了
Enough!
打電話給你的證人
Call your witness.
辯方稱...
The defense calls...
-吉米•洛根承認了  -什么
-Jimmy Logan to the stand.  -What?
事件驚喜的出現了轉機
In a surprise twist of events,
證人的出面
a witness came forward today
終止對我的當事人
and ended the prosecution's case
克林頓•戴維斯的起訴
against Clinton Davis.
證人看見受害人 塞西爾•阿克曼
The witness saw the victim, Cecil Ackerman,
被一個肇事逃逸的司機撞倒
mowed down by a hit-and-run driver
是一輛紅色S.U.V. 任傷者躺在路上不管
in a red S.U.V. And left on the road to die.
隨后 他撥打了911
He then called 911.
由此看來克林頓•戴維斯
It seems that Clinton Davis
不是這次事件唯一的好人
was not the only  good samaritan in this trial.
戴維斯先生
Mr. Davis?
我只是想希望你一切順利
I just wanted to wish you all the best.
是的  這就像你說的
Yeah, it's like you said
如果我是無辜的  一切都會水落石出
if I was innocent, everything would work out.
是的 我說過
Yes, I did.
所以 現在怎么樣
So what happens now?
-你回到你的生活  -不  不  不
-You go back to your life.  -No no no,
我的意思是 肇事逃逸者
I mean with the hit-and-run driver,
只要有一個目擊證人
the one the witness saw.
也許他就會自首
Maybe he'll turn himself in.
是你 你會嗎
Would you?
我他媽的愛你  你他媽的婊子
I fucking love you,  you fucking bitch!
-婊子  -別鬧了
-Whore!  -Stop it!
-我他媽的殺了你 -別鬧了
-I'll fucking kill you!  -Stop it!
-不  別煩我  -不要這樣對我  你個婊子
-No! Leave me alone!  -Don't do this to me, you fucking bitch!
我他媽的真的愛你
I fucking love you!
-嘿  -混蛋 讓我走
-Hey!  -Fucking let me go!
我他媽的愛你
I fucking love you!
佩德羅•岡薩雷斯的尸體
The mutilated  body of Pedro Gonzales
今天一大早在芝加哥河銀行被發現
was found early this morning on the bank of the Chicago river.
據驗尸官報告
According to a source at the coroner's office,
他的頭骨的后部被重力擊碎
the back of his skull was badly crushed,
兇器可能是一個錘子
possibly by a hammer.
他的家人說  最后一次看見他
His family says the last time anybody saw him alive
是上周六在北國商城
was at the north mall on Saturday.
我通過數據庫比對過一些關鍵字
I ran some keywords through the database.
顯示為一起未解殺人案
It flagged a string of unsolved homicides.
我不能呆在這
I can't stay here. Shit!
哦  他媽的 不 不
Oh fuck. No. No.
我看了尸檢結果
I looked at the autopsy results.
阿克曼上的傷口  和岡薩雷斯身上找到是相似的
The wounds on Ackerman were similar to those found on Gonzales.
阿克曼案子是一起肇事逃逸  還記得嗎
Ackerman was a hit-and-run, remember?
傷口不確定
The wounds were inconclusive.
在法庭上是你自己指出  親口說出來的
You yourself pointed that out at the trial.
尚無定論 確切的說
Inconclusive, exactly.
要么它是兩者兼而有之
What if it was both?
阿克曼跑到路上
What if Ackerman ran into the path of a car
他試圖擺脫戴維斯
because he was trying to get away from Davis
是誰折磨他致死
who was in the process of torturing him?
這解釋不了現場的混亂
It explains why the forensics was so confusing.
還有別的嗎
Anything else?
謝謝你來告訴我這些
Thanks for coming by.
嘿
Hey.
哦  媽的
Oh fuck.
先生......
Yes sir...
哦  媽的
Oh shit.
-是啊 你好  -你拿到照片了
-Yeah, hello.  -You get my photograph?
-你要干什么  -別再盯著我不放
-What do you want?  -Stop following me.
我知道你做了什么
I know what you did.
可警方不是還沒來電話
And yet the cops haven't come a'calling.
為什么你認為是我呢  米奇
Why you think that is, Mitch?
如果你知道我是司機
If you knew I was the driver,
為什么你沒有把我扯進來  嗯
why didn't you just turn me in, huh?
在警局 我不想拿出我的王牌
I didn't want to play my ace in the police station.
我需要在法庭上用
I needed to go to court.
我得讓我的同行們組成的陪審團
I had to get a jury of my peers
看看你的卡  證明我是無辜的
to see your card, find me innocent.
你想要合理懷疑
You wanted double jeopardy.
游戲結束 這是一張免費通行證
Bingo. A free pass.
-但你沒有揭穿我  -沒有必要
-But you didn't expose me.  -There was no need.
我能看到你有良心危機
I could see you were having a crisis of conscience.
-這是一個混蛋的游戲  -遠非如此
-Is this a fucking game to you?  -Far from it.
我不會讓你就此逃脫
I won't let you get away with this.
不  你會的
Yeah, you will,
要么我毀了你
or I will ruin you.
那么  誰來保護瑞秋和Ella
Besides, who's gonna protect Rachel and Ella
當你因為肇事逃逸被抓起來  嗯
when you get locked up for hit-and-run, hmm?
你說什么
What did you say?
家庭是相當重的東西  米奇
Family is a precious thing, Mitch.
這是我們的職責  對我們男人來說
It's our job as men
保護家人
to protect 'em.
戴維斯
Davis.
嘿 關上門
Hey. Shut the door.
那不是阿克曼
Is that Ackerman?
新聞上的那家伙
And the guy from the news.
必須找出所有這些人有什么關聯
Have to work out  what links all these men.
他是怎么挑選受害者  還有為什么
How he's picking his victims and why.
誰怎么選擇
How who's picking them?
克林頓•戴維斯
Clinton Davis.
什么
What?
這些都是未解殺人案
These are  the unsolved homicides
那加隆認為 拘禁戴維斯
that Kanon thinks match Davis's M.O.
拘禁戴維斯
Davis's M.O.?
戴維 戴維斯是無辜的
Dav-Davis was innocent.
肇事逃逸 米奇 打911報警者已經證明了這一點
Hit-and-run, Mitch. 911 caller proved it.
我懂  我覺得沒那么簡單
Yeah, I wish it were that simple.
這他媽到底是怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
他媽的什么情況  米奇
What the hell is going on, Mitch?
之前你接了戴維斯的案子 幾乎讓自己丟掉資格
First you blow the Davis case, almost get yourself disbarred
而現在呢 你想證明
and now what? You're trying to prove
這家伙是 該死的波士頓扼殺者
that this guy is the goddamn Boston strangler?
斯圖  如果我能解釋這一點  我會的
Stu, if I could explain this, I would.
病理學家是憑借什么認定這些工具
With what pathologists think were tools.
類似八個月前
The first took place  eight months
戴維斯全家被折磨時使用的工具
after Davis's family was tortured with similar tools.
看見了吧  我認為他選擇了他們
You see, I think he picked 'em.
我覺得他選擇了所有的人
I think he picked all of them,
可他媽的他們共同點是什么
but what the fuck  do they all have in common?
你看吧  阿克曼是一個兒童性騷擾者
Well, Ackerman was  a child molester.
其他的人都不是
None of the others were.
嗯  他們都是有犯罪記錄
Well, they do all have criminal records.
那么 你認為 這種行為開始于
So you think this behavior started
家人的死亡 對吧 -是的  我想是的
with the death of his family, right?  -Yes, I do.
所以 讓我想想那里發生了什么
So remind me-what happened there?
一名男子闖進他們的家
A man broke into their home
不斷地折磨
and systematically tortured
屠殺他的妻子和孩子......
and butchered his wife and child...
用了殺這些家伙類似的工具
using similar tools to the ones that killed these guys.
還讓戴維斯觀看了整個過程
The guy made Davis watch the whole goddamn thing.
然后他切開他的喉嚨離開 讓他自生自滅
Then he slit his throat and left him for dead.
他活了下來 這是一個奇跡
It was a miracle he survived.
這家伙的名字叫  伊曼紐爾•弗萊
The guy's name was Emanuel Fryer-
職業罪犯
career criminal;
槍殺的第二天晚上  另一家被入侵
gunned down the following night during another home invasion;
最近被假釋  等等
recently paroled; Blah blah blah.
入室行兇 哦  媽的
-Broken home oh shit.
什么
What?
岡薩雷斯  最近假釋
Gonzales, recently paroled.
費萊  最近假釋
Fryer, recently paroled.
阿克曼  也是最近
Ackerman  was recently
所有這些人都是最近他媽的假釋犯
all these men are recently fucking paroled.
斯圖  你他媽的就是個天才
Stu, you are a goddamn genius!
媽的 我愛你 愛死你了
Shit.I love you. I love you.
好了  你說
Okay, so you're saying
唯一的原因  阿克曼是在大街上
that the only reason Ackerman was in the street
是因為 戴維斯在追殺他
was because Davis was chasing him.
-嗯  -然后你離開后
-Uh-huh.  -And then after you left,
-戴維斯終結了  -完美推斷
-Davis finished the job?  -Exactly.
如果我能找到證據  你知道嗎
If I could just get proof, you know?
戴維斯無法從阿克曼案子開脫
Davis can't be retried for Ackerman,
但如果我能得到的證據表明  他 -
but if I can get evidence that he-
他殺死了其他那些人
he killed those other guys,
我可以把我們雙方的交易
I can cut us both a deal.
你在宣誓說了什么  我就做了什么 -
What you said under oath,  what I did-
你沒事嗎
You all right there?
-我所做的  它只是消失
-What I did,  it just goes away.
米奇  我在假釋中
Mitch, I'm on parole.
我卻要闖入一個他媽的家伙的家里
I get busted breaking into some guy's fucking house-
幫個忙吧  我不要你進去  我自己來
come on, I don't want you breaking in. I'll break in.
我只要你跟蹤他
I just need for you to tail him,
告訴他什么時候回來就行
let me know when he's coming back.
啊  那么它只是小小協助及教唆犯罪
Ah, it's just a little aiding and abetting then.
誒
Eh.
算了  米奇
Forget it, Mitch.
這樣吧 我答應你
Let it go. I'm done.
這混蛋真的闖進入你家
That fucker really break into your house?
是
Yes.
當我們正在睡覺
While we were sleeping.
好吧  他要知道你的旅程
All right,he's gonna know your ride.
你可以借給我輛干凈的車子嗎
Can you rent me a clean set of wheels?
當然
Of course.
謝謝你  吉米
Thanks, Jimmy.
你知道嗎  我的意思是
You know what?  I mean that.
我可能是一個混蛋  但我還是你的哥哥
I may be an asshole, but I'm still your brother.
再見  戴維斯
See you later, Davis.
好吧  伙計  再見
All right, guys.See you later.
晚安
Have a good evening.
-呦  吉米
-Yo, Jimmy.
找到什么了
Got anything  tying him to the victims?
不 還沒有
No. Not yet.
貌似他在這里吃飯和睡覺  僅此而已
Looks like he eats and sleeps  here, but that's about it.
其余時間  他都花在自助團體
The rest of the time he spends in self-help groups.
你知道 有時他一個晚上去兩次
You know, sometimes he goes to two a night.
哦  他媽的  找到了
Oh fuck. That's it.
這就是挑選的受害者
That's how he picks his victims.
殺死他家人的是一個假釋犯
The guy that killed his family was a parolee.
他們都在假釋期
They're all parolee meetings.
沒人注意到這個家伙煮咖啡
Nobody notices the guy making coffee.
他像暀W的蒼蠅掛起
He just hangs around like a fly on the wall,
監聽他 擔心這個家伙再犯罪
listening for the guy who feels worried about re-offending.
是啊  我一直去
Yeah, I've been to those meetings.
-這些人房間里全這樣  -沒錯
-The room's full of guys like that.  -Exactly.
他媽的
Fuck me.
他保留了假釋卡
He kept their parolee cards.
吉米  那是什么
Jimmy, what's that?
呃  我們附近有個水泥工地
Uh, we're near the cement works.
應該是休息時間
Must be coffee break or something.
你知道么 很近的
You know, that's pretty close.
是他回來了嗎
Is he coming back?
我不知道 他走進一個舊倉庫
I don't know. He went into some old warehouse
又出來拿著什么東西  不知道他去哪了
and came out carrying something.I lost him.
-看著像一些舊工具什么的  -盯好了
-Looked like some old tools or something.  -Get the fuck outta there.
吉米 吉米
Jimmy? Jimmy!
吉米  能聽到我說話嗎
Jimmy, can you hear me?
吉米 吉米 你在嗎
Jimmy?  Jimmy, are you there?
我來了 吉米
I'm coming, Jimmy.
吉米
Jimmy!
-吉米  -啊哈  他媽的
-Jimmy!  -Aah! Fuck!
吉米
Jimmy!
-米奇  -吉米
-Mitch!  -Jimmy!
救我
Help me!
你得救我  米奇
-You gotta help me, Mitch!
救我...米奇
Help... Mitch.
呦  吉米
Yo, Jimmy!
哦  請救我
Oh, please help me!
-吉米  -米奇
-Jimmy!  -Mitch!
米奇
Mitch!
哦  上帝
Oh, Jesus Christ.
杰米
Oh Jimmy.
這是911報警中心 有什么緊急情況
911, what is your emergency?
幫幫我
Help me.
救救我吧  謝謝
Help me, please.
他想殺了我
He's trying to kill me.
-快點  -先生
-Hurry.  -Sir?
先生 誰要殺你
Sir, who is trying to kill you?
先生 先生 你在嗎
Sir? Sir, are you there?
先生
Sir?
喂  是啊 我需要一輛救護車
Hello? Yeah, I need an ambulance.
你能聽到 -你能聽到我嗎
Can you hear-can you hear me?
你好
Hello?
是的 我需要一輛救護車
Yeah, I need an ambulance.
-靠  他媽的
-Fuck! Fuck!
-別丟下我  -我要搬動你  好嗎
-Stay with me. I'm gonna move you, okay?  -
-好吧  -來吧
-Okay?  -Okay.
好 好 來吧
Okay okay, come on.
來吧 留在我身邊
Come on, stay with me!
來吧
Come on!
我們走  伙計
Let's go, men.
嘿
Hey!
-嘿  他需要救護車  -放他下來
-Hey, he needs an ambulance.  -Set him down now!
-哦  他媽的  -把按住
-Oh fuck. -Put him down!
-快點  -放下他
-Do it!  -Put him down now!
-快點  快放下  -操
-Now! Down! Down!  -Fuck.
你他媽的跟我開玩笑 哦 混蛋
You gotta be fucking kidding me. Oh fuck.
快
Go!
-他需要救護車  -好了
-He needs an ambulance!  -Cool it!
吉米  上帝  叫他媽的救護車
Jimmy. Oh God, get him a fucking ambulance!
吉米  躺下 就躺那  兄弟
Jimmy, hang in there. Hang in there, brother.
-堅持住  兄弟  -...會人救你......
-Hang in there, brother.  -...can and will be used against you...
-冷靜  -躺在那里
-Calm down.  -Hang in there.
你有權請律師
You have the right to an attorney.
我們已經找到一個受傷的白人男性
We've got an injured white male.
-吉米怎樣  -他還在昏迷中...
-How's Jimmy?  -He's in a coma...
......醫生說有希望
..but the doctors are hopeful.
你要告訴我你們的關系嗎
So you wanna tell me what your relationship is to him?
是的  我們  嗯......
Yeah, we're, um...
是同母異父兄弟
step-brothers.
我們的父母只是未正式結婚
Our parents just never married.
這就是為什么他會在法庭上為你說謊
That's why he'd lie for you in court.
沒錯
Exactly.
那么 為什么現在這樣對他
So why turn on him now?
什么
What?
他勒索你了
Was he blackmailing you?
你在說什么
What are you talking about?
不是我干的
I didn't do this.
克林頓•戴維斯干的
Clinton Davis did this.
-用你的錘子  -是的
-Using your hammer?  -Yes.
他闖進我家  偷走了我的工具
He broke into my house, he stole my tools.
你有沒有報案
Did you report that?
-沒有  -沒有
-No.  -No.
錘子有你的指紋
It's only your prints on the hammer.
上帝
Jesus Christ.
我打了911報警電話  上帝做證
I made the 911 call, for Christ's sakes.
我為什么要這么做  如果我是有罪的
Why would I do that if I was guilty?
我真的不知道  米奇
I really don't know, Mitch.
可你之前這么干過
But you did it before.
911  有什么緊急情況
911, what's your emergency?
我需要一輛救護車  一個男士被車撞了
I need an ambulance. A guy's been hit by a car.
在什么位置  先生
What's the location, sir?
呃  基勒
Uh, Keeler.
-這是你  對不對  -是的 是的  是的  是我
-That's you, right?  -Yes yes yes, it's me.
我開車撞了阿克曼  然后走了
I hit Ackerman with my car and I left.
這是錯誤的 我知道 因為我很害怕
It was wrong.I know that, but I was scared.
我喝了酒 這是一個交通意外
I'd been drinking. It was an accident.
我們找到了這個...
We found this...
就在你的工具箱的底部
in the bottom of your toolbox.
沾滿了阿克曼的血跡
It has Ackerman's blood  all over it.
一定是戴維斯故意把它放在那里的
Well, Davis must've  put it there.
我幫助阿克曼時 我的卡掉在了現場
I dropped my cards when I was helping Ackerman.
-我一定是掉了一個  -所有的這些證據...
-I must've missed one.  -All of this...
-直接與你有關  -哦  天
-leads directly to you.  -Oh, Jesus Christ.
好了 聽我說  好嗎 如果我殺了阿克曼
All right, listen, okay? If I killed Ackerman,
為什么我沒有釘死戴維斯
why didn't I crucify Davis in court
法庭上當時我有機會  嗯
when I had the chance, hmm?
他是完美的替罪羊
He was the perfect scapegoat.
好吧  這有一個袋子
Okay, there's a bag.
-有個袋子  -是的
-There's a bag?  -Yes.
戴維斯保留的 所有的受害者的I.D.S
Davis kept the I.D.S  of all his victims.
他針對暴力假釋者
He's targeting violent parolees
他認為應該重新定罪
that he thinks will re-offend,
就像殺害他的家人
like the man that killed his family.
-包在哪里  -在他家
-Where's this bag?  -In his house.
你怎么知道的
How do you know this?
-我去過  -你去過
-I broke in.  -You broke in?
你闖進了他房子里
You broke into his fucking house?
事情嚴重了  米奇...
Seriously, Mitch...
我怎么知道 不是你把它放在那里
How do I know you didn't put it there?
你知道  我不會再回答任何問題
You know, I don't think I should answer any more questions
直到有律師在場
till I have a lawyer present.
你知道  我想
You know, I think
這真是一個非常好的想法
that's a really good idea.
你的電話 斯圖爾特•威爾遜從D.A.的辦公室打來的
You've got a call-Stuart Wilson from the D.A.'s office.
斯圖  你他媽的去哪了
Stu, where the fuck have you been?
對不起  米奇
I'm sorry, Mitch.
這是他們唯一的讓我和你談談的方式
This is the only way they'd let me talk to you.
現在你聽我說 你他媽的王八蛋
Now you listen to me, you fucking son of a bitch.
我會找到你  我會來的  我會取你性命
I will find you, I will come for you and I will take your life.
-你聽到了么 戴維斯  -哦  聽著呢
-You hear me, Davis?  -Oh, listen to you.
當你打Ackerman的時候  你的決心在哪
Where was all that backbone  when you hit Ackerman, huh?
如果你曾表露過決心
If you'd showed it then,
你就會一直等到救護車到來 這樣他也不會死
you would've waited for the ambulance and he'd be alive.
當然 他還是會不被約束的
Course, he'd still be free
-到處去傷害孩子們...
-to go around hurting small children...
-...這也是我帶走他時他正在做的
-...which he was about  to do when I took him.
你其實是知道的 對吧
You do know that, right?
如果你讓他好好的一個人呆著
If you'd let well enough alone,
我們永遠也不會來到這個地方 米奇
we never would've come to this place, Mitch.
你想干什么
What do you want?
你可以毀了我的生活
You could've ruined my life
或毀了你的
or ruined yours,
但你卻發現 第三個選項
but yet you found a third option.
一是幫助我們兩個
One that helped us both.
有沒有他媽的第三個選項
There is no fucking third option here.
是啊  有
Yeah, there is.
如果在他們拘禁你的同時
What if another murder happened  with the same M.O.
發生了另一起相同手法的謀殺怎么辦
While they have you  in custody, hmm?
走向清白的道路是漫長的
Go a long way towards shedding light on your innocence
即使是因內疚給出一個合理的懷疑
or even throw a reasonable doubt on your guilt.
你說什么  你在說什么
What are you-what are you talking about,
-另一起兇殺案么  -問題是
-another murder?  -The problem is
你不知道我的痛
you don't know my pain
還有我的空虛
or my emptiness.
可現在你要知道為什么是我
But now you're going  to know what it is to be me.
戴維斯 戴維斯 是什么...
Davis?  Davis, what...?
你在哪里 戴維斯 嗯
Where are you, Davis? Huh?
我現在得走了 米奇
I have to go now, Mitch.
戴維斯
Davis!
嘿  掉線了 嘿
Hey! Is the line cut? Hey!
我要打個電話  我要往外打個電話
I need a line. I need an outside line.
-戴維斯要殺我妻子  -停
-Davis is going to kill my wife! -Stop!
-嘿  -那混蛋會殺了我的妻子
-Hey! -He's gonna kill my fucking wife.
-Brockden夫人  -我是
-Mrs. Brockden?  -Yes.
我是加隆警官  我不想打擾你
I'm Detective Kanon. I hate to bother you
在這痛苦的時刻  但我想問你幾個
at this ungodly hour, but I'd like to ask you
有關你丈夫的問題...
some questions about your husband...
......如果可以的話
...if it's  all right with you.
沒事  當然 -我
No, not at all. Of co-I'm-
就一會兒
just one minute.
犯罪嫌疑人 大約55  ...
Suspect is approximately 5'5"...
你知道  我打了一天的電話  我 -
You know, I've been calling all day and I-
我希望你不介意
I hope you don't mind.
嘿  警官  剛剛見了一個客戶
Hey, officer. Just finished up with a client.
你能告訴我 為什么逮捕我丈夫
Can you tell me what you've arrested my husband for?
-謀殺  -什么
-Murder.  -What?!
我的意思是 這是瘋了 米奇
That-I mean,that's insane. Mitch
我知道 我知道  -這是瘋了
I know.I know it  -it's crazy.
我個人相信他是無罪的
And I personally don't believe he's guilty at all,
但我只需要問你幾個問題 以便澄清
but I just need to ask you some questions to clear-
你能給我倒杯水嗎
Could you get me a glass of water, please?
嗯 是的 當然可以
Um, yeah, sure.
晚安 律師先生
Good night,counselor.
小心開車
Drive safe.
你說的沒錯
There you go.
你看 我只是不明白
Look, I just don't understand.
如果你知道他沒有那么做 你為什么還拘押著他
If you know that he didn't do it, then why are you still holding him?
其他偵探對他的事情也有不解之處
Some of the other detectives are having a problem with his story.
就像我說的 我們曾經談過
But like I said, once we have our conversation,
我確定可以澄清一切
I'm sure we can clear that all up.
-他接了個電話就瘋了  -誰打來的
-He got a phone call and he went crazy.  -Who called?
威爾遜什么的 好像是從D.A.的辦公室
Wilson or something from the D.A.'s office.
他咆哮著撥打了另一個電話
He was ranting about making another call,
有人說是要殺他的妻子 戴維斯
said someone was gonna kill his wife. Davis.
什么情況
What the hell's going on in here?
-剛剛是你打電話給米奇  -不是
-Did you just call Mitch?  -No.
申請支援 去Brockden家 快
Get a unit over to Brockden's house now.
瑞秋  瑞秋
Rachel! Rach!
哦  有人么 誰來救救我
Oh, somebody! Somebody help me!
-起來  -不  你為什么要這么做
-Get up. -No! Why are you doing this?
-起來  -不
-Get up.  -No!
請  不要殺我
Please, don't kill me.
-不要  -不要傷害她
-No. -Don't hurt her!
米奇 米奇
Mitch. Mitch.
槍扔過來
Toss the gun over here.
快點
Do it.
雷切爾 我要你彎腰
Now, Rachel, I want you to bend down
拿著槍管 撿起來
take that gun by the barrel
交給我
and pass it to me.
不管你想怎樣 克林頓 結束吧
Whatever you're thinking of doing, Clinton, don't do it.
別說沒用的 是你自己搞砸了
Well, it looks like you just fucked up
我們合理的疑問 米奇
our reasonable doubt here, Mitch.
你的家庭發生了什么可怕的事
What happened to your family was terrible.
這樣做  改變不了這一切
Doing this, it's-it's not gonna change that.
我那是在保護別人的家人不再受傷害
I was protecting other people's families.
現在誰在保護你的家人 米奇
Who's gonna  protect yours now, Mitch?
你么
You?
現在你懂了嗎 會有人救你嗎
You understand now? Do you get it?
是啊  我懂了
Yeah, I get it.
我知道你的妻子和孩子
I get that you watched your wife and child
被折磨致死  而你什么也沒做
tortured to death and you did nothing.
你就是個他媽的懦夫
I get that you're a fucking coward.
沒話說了吧
You froze.
你關心自己勝過自己的親骨肉
You cared more about saving yourself than your own flesh and blood.
-米奇  別說了  -你認為找出
-Mitch, please don't  -You think if you take out
盡可能多的假釋犯...  -閉嘴
-as many parolees as possible...  -Shut up.
你的家人就不會死了
...you'll make what happened to your family go away.
-別說了  -你知道 如果你還是一個男人...
-Please. -You know, if you were a man...
一個真正的男人 你應該先死
a real man, you would've died first.
我已經死過了
I thought I was dead.
四肢被綁著  喉嚨被切開
I was hog-tied  with my throat cut
我是那么的不幸
but I wasn't so lucky.
親眼看著家人折磨死去
I had to watch my loved ones die.
不過 你沒有被綁  米奇
You're not tied up though, Mitch.
那么 你要怎么選擇
So what are you gonna do, huh?
你愿意先去死
Are you willing to die first?
我愿意
Yes.
是的  我可以
Yes, I am.
我們看看吧
We'll see about that.
哦  米奇  不
Oh! Mitch! No!
你要體驗
You need to understand,
看著你愛的人
to see someone you love
流血過多 死在您的眼前 是什么感覺
bleed to death in front of your eyes.
不要 住手
Please. Please don't.
-不要開槍  -乞求是沒用的 雷切爾
-Please don't. -Begging won't help, Rachel.
我妻子也乞求過
My wife begged.
這是在浪費時間
It's a waste of time.
-現在.. -不  不要
-Now..-No! No!
很快你就會體驗到我的感受了
Now you're gonna see what it's like to be me.
拜托
Please!
感受到我一樣的空虛
To feel my emptiness,
一樣的痛苦
my pain.
會給你一些從來沒有過的東西 米奇
I'm gonna give you something I never had, Mitch.
來證明你可以做的比我更好
Prove you can  do better than I did.
-請  -開槍吧
-Please. -Go ahead.
-拯救...你的家人
-Save... your family.
米奇 不
Mitch, no!
米奇
Mitch!
要我扶你嗎
Can I help you with anything?
哦  太可笑了
Oh, you're hysterical.
瑞秋
Rach!
瑞秋 他來了
Rach, he's here.
艾拉給我  打個招呼吧
Give me Ella, then you can say hello.
-我來抱會  -知道了
-Yeah, I got her.  -I know.
-我妻子 蕾切爾  -嘿
-This is my wife Rachel.  -Hey.
我的兄弟吉米
This is my brother Jimmy.
-你好  吉米  -哇  你好
-Hello, Jimmy.  -Wow, hi.
-你還好嗎  -比我想的好多了
-How are you?  -Better than I look.
這是...
And this...
-天哦  -這是你的侄女......
-Oh Jesus.  -This is your niece...
艾拉
Ella.
哦  太可愛了 你好  艾拉
Oh my God. Hi, Ella.
艾拉  那是你的叔叔吉米
Ella, that's your Uncle Jimmy.
嘿  艾拉
Hey, Ella.
哦  太可愛了
Oh my God.
哦  米奇
Oh, Mitch.
你給她起個小名
You named her after your ma.
太棒了
Wow.
嗨  你們兩家伙別傻站了
Well, I don't know about you guys,
-我都要凍僵了  -是啊
-but I am freezing.  -Yeah.
-吉米 可以請你進來嗎  -是啊  好 很榮幸
-Jimmy, wanna come in?  -Yeah, all right. Definitely.
-抱著她沒問題吧  -有點緊張
-You okay with her?  -This is terrifying.
你怎么做到這一點
How do you do this?